Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode. Subtitles will likely not function properly. Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv: https://mpv.io
.مشغل الفيديو الخاص بك لا يدعم صيغة ملف الترجمة المستخدمة في هذه الحلقة .من المحتمل ألا تعمل الترجمة بشكل صحيح يرجى استخدام أحد مشغلات الفيديو :على سبيل المثال mpv الموصى بها، كمشغل https://mpv.io/
Video Editing
مونتاج
Feeso Galaxy 9000
Feeso Galaxy 9000
Soundtracking
الصوت
Halee
Halee
Graphics
جرافيك
Datenshi
Datenshi
Quality Control
ضبط الجودة
Gab Galaxy 9000 Gol D. Rocks Grug Mr. Luffy Pepperjack Westfal Zenef
Gab Galaxy 9000 Gol D. Rocks Grug Mr. Luffy Pepperjack Westfal Zenef
Karaoke
كاريوكي
KaitouYahiko
Rocks-Team NightBaronTeam
Timing
مزامنة الترجمة
Gab
Gab Raven-
Subtitle Editing
التدقيق اللغوي
CraigyBoi Kustogg Polly Lil T Zenef Yag
FiberAhmed
Raws
الخام
Neo-Raws
Neo-Raws
Translation
ترجمة
Funimation Nikki PamkinPinguin roi
Crunchyroll
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode. Subtitles will likely not function properly. Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv: https://mpv.io
.مشغل الفيديو الخاص بك لا يدعم صيغة ملف الترجمة المستخدمة في هذه الحلقة .من المحتمل ألا تعمل الترجمة بشكل صحيح يرجى استخدام أحد مشغلات الفيديو :على سبيل المثال mpv الموصى بها، كمشغل https://mpv.io/
Alright.
اسمعوا، سيهاجمون من هذا الساحل عند الفجر
and that the only route into the village from here is this slope.
.والطريق الوحيد إلى الجزيرة هو هذا المنحدر
The cliffs are too steep everywhere else.
،الباقي كلّه جروف .ممّا يعني أنّهم لن يستطيعوا اجتيازها
The Slope
المنحدر
In other words, if we defend this slope at all costs,
بمعنى آخر، إن تمكنّا من ،من تأمين هذا المنحدر
the village will be safe!
!فلن يطال القرية أي اعتداء
Oh! That's easy!
!فهمت! هذا بسيط
It's easy to say, but we still have to fight!
الكلام سهل، ولكن يقع !الباقي على قوتنا
What can you guys do?
ما الذي تستطيعون فعله؟
Cut.
.التقطيع
Stretch.
.التمدد
Steal.
.السرقة
I can hide.
.أنا أستطيع الاختباء
– You're gonna fight!
!أنت ستقاتل
I was just kidding, c'mon!
!إنّي أمزح! يا إلهي
Oh, Klahadore!
!كلاهادور-سان
Welcome back!
!مرحبًا بعودتك
How is Miss Kaya?
كيف حال الآنسة؟
She's resting now.
.إنّها نائمة
The whole affair really wore her out...
...بدت متعبة للغاية
To think such a thing happened while I was in the neighboring town...
كيف لذلك أن يحدث ...أثناء ذهابي للمدينة المجاورة
That Usopp boy certainly is a troublemaker.
.ذلك الصبي أوسوب مزعج حقًا
Indeed...
...أجل
And claiming you were a pirate of all things…
،وعلاوة على كلّ هذا ...ادعى أنّك قرصان
It's not even a good lie!
!يا لها من كذبة غير معقولة
Is that so...?
.صحيح
What is this?
ما هذا؟
Oh, that is a present from the miss to you.
.هديةُ لك من الآنسة
She said it's your third year at the mansion,
،بمناسبة سنتك الثالثة في هذا القصر
so it's a sort of commemoration.
.لذا فإنّه احتفال تذكاري
A commemoration...
...احتفال تذكاري
Your current glasses seem to slip often,
،نظارتك الحالية تنزلق كثيرًا
so she custom-ordered those!
!!لذا فقد طلبت هذه لتُصمم خصيصًا لك
She's such a nice, thoughtful person!
!يا لها من فتاة لطيفة ومراعية
A commemoration, you say...?
أقلت تذكاري؟
Indeed, tomorrow is a day to commemorate.
.سيكون يوم الغد تذكاريًّا فعلًا
Huh?
ماذا؟
It's a crescent moon tonight.
.القمر هلال هذه الليلة
Nights like this make my heart race...
،ليالٍ كهذه تجعل نبضات قلبي تتسارع
and my blood stir...
...ودمي يثور
K-Klahadore!
!كـ-كلاهادور-سان
Wh-Why did you break Miss Kaya's gift?!
مـ-ما الذي تفعل بهديتها؟
A gift? Oh, I'll be accepting a gift, all right...
.سأقبل الهدية
but not this paltry trinket.
...ولكن ليس شيئًا كهذا !بل هذا القصر بأكمله
Wh-What are you saying?!
!مـ-ما الذي تقوله؟
I guess there's no need to continue this charade.
.لا داعي للاستمرار بالتمثيل
There's going to be an accident in a few hours, anyway...
ستقع حادثة بعد بضع ...ساعات على أيّ حال
It truly has been a long three years!
!كانت ثلاث سنوات طويلة حقًا
Miss Kaya! Run!
!اهربي يا آنستي
Captain Jango!
!قبطان جانغو
It's almost daybreak! Please wake up, Captain Jango!
!سيحين الفجر بعد قليل !استيقظ رجاءً أيها القبطان جانغو
Good morning, Captain!
!صباح الخير يا قبطان
Good morning!
!صباح الخير
You morons!
!أيّها الحمقى
My policy is to say "good morning" when the sun is up!
سياستي هي قول صباح الخير !بعد شروق الشمس
Looks like he's in a bad mood.
.يبدو بمزاج سيّئ
He did just wake up...
...ذلك لأنّه استيقظ للتو
Look!
!انظروا
The moon's still up, and it's the middle of the night.
لا يزال القمر مرتفعًا !وما زلنا في منتصف الليل
How dare you raise your voices!
!كيف تصرخون هكذا؟
– Our apologies, sir! We're sorry, sir!
!نعتذر! متأسفون
Alright then, good morning.
!لا بأس إذًا، صباح الخير جميعًا
Now, men!
!يا رجال
"One-Two" Jango Acting Captain of the Black Cat Pirates
«الملقب بـ«جانغو، واحد-اثنان مُكلف بقيادة قراصنة القط الأسود
Set sail!
!إبحار
– Aye, aye!
!حسنًا
Alright! Perfect!
!حسنًا، انتهيت
They won't be able to climb up this slope anymore...
لن يتمكنوا من .صعود المنحدر الآن
thanks to all the oil we've poured on it!
.بفضل الزيت الذي سكبناه هنا
We'll attack 'em while they slip and slide around!
.سنوقعهم عن المنحدر ثم نجهز عليهم
Oil, huh...?
زيت إذًا؟
No matter what, we will protect this slope!
على أيّ حال، سنحمي هذا !المنحدر مهما كلّف الأمر
Let's just hope that none of us slip down there.
لنأمل ألّا يحدث نقيض ذلك .وننزلق بدورنا
It'd be pretty dumb to get caught in our own trap.
.الوقوع بفخٍ نصبناه بأنفسنا لَحماقةٌ
You sure did come up with a slick plan!
تذهلني مقدرتك على التفكير !بفعل أشياء لعوبة كهذه
O-Of course!
!بالطبع
I have complete confidence in my slingshot and daring ideas!
!بجرأتي ومقلاعي، يقيني لا يتزعزع
It's almost dawn.
.يكاد يبزغ الفجر
Any moment now.
.سيأتون
We're here!
!وصلنا
Alright!
!حسنًا يا رجال، اقتحموا القرية
– Yeah!
!حسنًا
Captain! There are a couple of strange boats here!
!أيّها القبطان، هناك قاربان غريبان هنا
What?!
!ماذا؟
Should we check 'em out?
هل أذهب لأتحققهما؟
Leave 'em.
.اتركهما
I doubt they've got treasure.
!أستبعد أن بحوزتهم ثروة
Where are they? The sky's all bright now.
أين هم؟ !فالشمس أشرقت
Maybe they overslept or something?
ربما استغرقوا في النوم .أو شيءُ كهذا
Say...
...بالمناسبة
Maybe it's just me,
أهذه مخيلتي؟
but I swear I hear shouting coming from somewhere...
!أسمع صوتًا ما
Yeah, I definitely hear something!
!أسمع صوت فعلًا
N-Now that you mention it...
...بالمناسبة
Hey! What is it?!
!ما الخطب؟
There's a place just like this to the north!
!هناك مكانُ كهذا في الشمال أيضًا
Don't tell me…!
...لا يمكن
You mean this is the wrong shore?!
!أتعني أنّ هذا الساحل الخطأ؟
This is where they had their secret meeting, so I just assumed...
.جرى اجتماعهما السري هنا، فافترضتُ ذلك
Hey, hurry! They're gonna reach the village! Where is this place?!
!لنسرع !سيدخلون القرية! أين ذلك المكان؟
If you run straight north from here, you'll get there in three minutes!
إن ركضت شمالًا مباشرة من هنا !فستصل خلال ثلاث دقائق
It looks basically the same, so we just need to stop them at the slope there!
.شبيهُ بهذا المكان، علينا إيقافهم عند المنحدر
Hold on...
ماذا؟
Oh no!
!مصيبة
The north shore is where our boats are!
الساحل الشمالي هو !مكان وجود قاربينا
They'll take our treasure!
!سيسلبون كنزنا
I'll get there in twenty seconds!
!سأذهب إلى هناك خلال 20 ثانية
Dammit!
!سحقًا
My brilliant oil trap was all for nothing!
!فسدت خطة الزيت العبقريّة خاصتي
My treasure...
...كنزي
Hey!
!أنتِ
What're you doing? Let's go!
!ماذا تفعلين؟ لنذهب
Yeah! We have to hurr–
...أ-أجل! علينا أن نسر
Help! I'm slipping!
!ساعدني! سأسقط
Let go, you moron!
!اتركيني أيّتها الغبيّة
Sorry!
!آسفة
Perfect!
!رائع
Thanks, Zoro!
.شكرًا لك يا زورو
Sorry! The treasure's in danger!
.آسفة، فالكنز في خطر
Try to get back up somehow!
.حاول الصعود بطريقة ما
That girl's gonna pay!
.لن أغفر لتلك المرأة
I won't let them enter the village!
!لن أسمح لهم بدخول القرية أبدًا
But man, Luffy sure runs fast...!
!ولكن لوفي سريع حقًا
I can't even see him anymore!
.لم أعد أراه أبدًا الآن
Straight north! Straight north! Straight north!
!مباشرة نحو الشمال !مباشرة نحو الشمال! مباشرة نحو الشمال
They're dead meat if they so much as touch my treasure!
.لن أغفر لهم إن لمسوا كنزي
Someone's at the top of the slope!
!هناك شخص على قمة التل
It's you!
!أنت
My name is Captain Usopp!
.اسمي هو القبطان أوسوب
I've been waiting for you all this time!
!كنت بانتظاركم هنا طوال الوقت
Wh-What the...? I'm the first one here?!
!مـ-ماذا، هل أنا أول الواصلين؟
But he was running way ahead of me!
.ولكنّه كان يسبقني بكثير
Dammit!
!سحقًا
What do I do?!
ما عليّ فعله؟
I can't climb up!
!لا أستطيع الصعود
I'm at the village now!
!بلغت القرية
That's weird!
!هذا غريب
He said north, so I ran in the coldest direction!
!قال الشمال، لذا ركضت نحو اتجاه بارد
You're that kid who overheard our plans. What do you think you're doing?
...أنت ذاك الفتى
I-I'm warning you!
!أ-أحذركم
Turn back while you still can!
!عودوا بما أنّ الفرصة سانحة لكم الآن
Or else my crew of 100 million men will beat the crap out of you guys!
وإلّا فإنّ رفاقي المئة مليون !سيبرحونكم ضربًا
A hundred million?
مئة مليون؟
Hey now, no one's falling for that!
!هذه أسوأ من كذبة أطفال
What?!
!ماذا؟ مئة مليون؟! مذهل
He's obviously lying, Captain!
!إنّه يكذب بالطبع أيّها القبطان
He's so gullible...
...يا له من ساذج
They saw through it?
!تبًا! كشفوني؟
He seriously thought he could fool us, too...
!ظن بإمكانه خداعنا
Why, you...!
أيّها الوغد
How dare you trick me!
!كيف تجرؤ على خداغي؟
Captain Jango! I have news!
!أيّها القبطان جانغو! أحملُ خبرًا
Really?! Is it bad?!
!أخبرُ سيئ؟
No! It's not bad!
!كلا
We found treasure on those strange boats!
!عثرنا على كنزٍ في تلك القوارب الغريبة
Lots of it, too!
!إنّه مقدار مذهل
Maybe four, no, five million berries!
!ربما 4، لا بل 5 ملايين بيري
What?!
!ماذا؟
F-Five million berries...?!
!خـ-خمسة ملايين بيري
Why do those guys have that much money on their boats?
لماذا توجد كلّ هذه هذه الأموال في قاربيهما؟
So you found my treasure!
!هذا كنزي
I'll let you have it!
!ولكن سأعطيه لكم
What?! You'll give us the treasure?!
!ماذا؟ ستعطينا الكنز؟
That's right!
!كما سمعتم
In exchange, all I ask is that you leave immediately!
،بمقابل ذلك الكنز !عودوا أدراجكم الآن
Wha...?!
!ماذا؟
Is he really trying to buy us off?
أتعتقد أنّ بإمكانك ردعنا مقابل المال؟
What a scummy guy!
!يا له من تصرف مشين
You fool...
.أحمق
We're pirates.
.نحن قراصنة
Of course we're going to take the treasure!
!سنأخذ الكنز بالطبع
But that's no reason for us to turn back.
ولكن ذلك ليس سببًا .كافيًا لأن نرجع
Y-You have a point...
...هـ-هذا صحيح
Alright, then! On "one, two, Jango," you'll let us pass!
إن فهمت، فافسح لنا !«الطريق بعد قولي «واحد، اثنان، جانغو
It's that weapon from before!
!هذا السلاح من تلك المرة
One, two...
...واحد، اثنان
Ja–
–جا
Quit saying stupid crap!
!كفَّ عن قول الترهات
Wh-Who's she?!
!مـ-من هذه المرأة؟
Captain! This is no time to hypnotize yourself and let people through!
أيّها القبطان، هذا ليس الوقت لأن !تنوّم نفسك مغناطيسيًا وتسمح للناس بالعبور
The treasure on those boats is mine!
!كنز ذلك القارب ملك لي
You won't get a single berry!
!لن أسمح لكم بأخذ ولا حتّى بيري واحد
Hold on to it for me because I'm coming for it!
!أمسكوا به جيّدًا !سآتي لأخذه الآن
That hurt!
!هذا مؤلم
Who said you could give them my treasure?!
!لماذا أعطيتهم كنزي دون إذني؟
Well, you didn't have to whack me!
!لا بأس بقولي لهم ذلك فحسب
What're you talking about?! I just saved you!
ما هذا الذي تقوله بعد أن أنقذتك؟
Huh?
ماذا؟
I forgot to mention, but don't look at his ring when he starts counting!
!نسيت إخبارك، لا تحدّق بحلقه حتّى النهايّة
He's a hypnotist!
!إنّه منوّم مغناطيسي
H-Hypnotist?!
!مـ-منوّم مغناطيسي؟
So, where's Luffy?
وإذًا، أين لوفي؟
He got here first, right?
ألم يكن أول من ركض؟
Dunno!
لا أدري، إمّا أنّه خاف !أو ضلّ الطريق
That'd mean he's lost.
.ضلّ الطريق إذًا
Man, just when we need him, too!
يا إلهي! كيف له أن يتوه !في وقت مهم كهذا؟
Alright, I'll take command.
.أنا سآخذ القيادة هنا
Go kick their butts! I'll cover you!
!اذهبي لضربهم، أنا سأدعمك
What?! Hold on! Why me?!
!لحظة، لماذا أنا؟
There's no way I can take on that huge army!
من المستحيل أن أواجه جيشًا !ضخمًا كهذا، فأنا ضعيفة
Don't be fooled just 'cause I'm a guy!
!كوني رجلًا لا يعني أنّي قويّ
I'm so scared that my legs are shaking like crazy! See?!
أنا خائف لدرجة أنّ رجلاي !ترتعشان بشكل لا يصدق! انظري
Big deal!
!وما بذلك؟
I'm so scared my eyes are tearing up!
انظر! أنا خائفة لدرجة !أنّ عيناي غارقتان بالدموع
Your eyes are bone dry!
!إنّهما جافتان بالكامل
If you're gonna lie, at least make it believable!
،إن كنتِ ستكذبين !فاجعليها أكثر واقعيّة
That's rich coming from you!
!لا أريد سماع هذا منك
We don't have time to deal with this...
.لا نملك الوقت للعبث معهما
Just trample over them and head for the village, men!
اسحقوهما فورًا وتقدموا !إلى القرية يا رجال
H-Here they come!
!إ-إنّهم قادمون
Oh, yeah!
!تذكرت
I have caltrops!
!لديّ فخاخ شائكة
So you do have some goodies!
!تملك أشياء جيدة إذًا
Gimme, gimme!
!أعطني، أعطني
Take this!
!خذوا هذه
Caltrop Hell!
!جحيم الفخاخ الشائكة
Damn you, Nami!
!سحقًا! تبًا لنامي
She's gonna pay for this!
!لن أغفر لها أبدًا
I made it!
!اجتزته
Wh-Which way is the north shore?!
!أ-أين هو الطريق شمالًا إلى الساحل؟
Straight north! Straight north! Straight north!
!مباشرة نحو الشمال !مباشرة نحو الشمال! مباشرة نحو الشمال
Which way is north?!
!أين هو الشمال؟
Oww!
!مؤلم
Alright! We got 'em!
!مرحى، نلنا منهم
Now, then...!
...والآن
Lethal Lead Star!
!القتل المؤكّد: النّجم الرّئيس
Bastard!
!وغد
Way to go!
!أحسنت
Keep it up, now!
!استمر على هذا المنوال
I'm gonna take a breather.
.سأنسحب قليلًا
But it hasn't even been five minutes!
!لم تقاتلي بعد حتّى
Wh-What is it?!
!ما الخطب؟
There are caltrops behind us too...
...هناك فخاخ شائكة خلفنا أيضًا
Are you stupid?!
!أيّتها الحمقاء
You dropped 'em there!
!أنتِ أسقطتِهم هنا
Outta the damn way!
!ابتعد عن طريقنا
Do you seriously think you can stop us?
أتعتقد أنّ بإمكانك إيقافنا حقًا؟
Let's go, guys!
!لنذهب جميعًا
Captain Kuro is waiting!
.القبطان كورو بانتظارنا
– Yeah!
!هيّا
Wh-What the...?!
!ما خطبه؟
Let go, you bastard! Dammit, let go!
!اتركني أيّها الوغد! اتركني
Damn you!
!أيّها الوغد
Take this! You bastard!
!تبًا لك! تبًا لك
I... can't...
...لا يمكنني
let you get past this slope.
...أن أسمح لكم بالعبور من هذا المنحدر
This is just another one of my lies...
...لأنّي كذبت كالعادة
so it'll be just another ordinary day for the village.
...ستحظى القرية بيوم عادي آخر فحسب
I absolutely will not let you pass!
!لذلك لن أسمح لكم بالعبور أبدًا
Damn brat! Shut up!
!اصمت أيّها الطفل اللعين
You bitch!
!أيّتها المرأة اللعينة
Oww!
!مؤلم
Are you...?!
...أنتِ
That's enough now!
!هذا يكفي
Hey, you guys!
!أنتم
Quit bothering with them and get going already!
!لا تبالوا بهما واذهبوا فورًا
Have you forgotten this is Captain Kuro's plan?!
هل نسيتم أنّ هذه !خطّة القبطان كورو؟
If anything derails it,
،إن حدث شيء يفسد الخطة
he'll kill every last one of us!
!فسنُقتل جميعًا
Do you understand that, you dumbasses?!
أتفهمون هذا أيّها الحمقى؟
W-Well, uh...
...أ-أنتم-
Yeah, let's hurry to the village!
!أجل، لنسرع إلى القرية
Stop...
...ا-انتظروا
Dammit...
...سحقًا
Stop!
!انتظر
Stop... Don't go to the village!
!انتظر... لا تذهبوا إلى القرية
Shut up!
!اصمت
Stop!
!توقفوا
Please...!
!...أترجاكم
Please don't kill everyone!
!لا تقتلوا الجميع..
I love this village!
!أحب هذه القرية
I want to protect it!
!أريد حمايتها
Wh-What is this, Captain Jango?!
!مـ-ما هذا أيّها القبطان جانغو؟
Nobody said the village had guys like these!
لم يذكر أحد وجود أشخاص !كهذين في القرية
About time...
...وصلا أخيرًا
Why the hell are these guys such pushovers?!
!ما هؤلاء الضعفاء؟
Beats me!
!لا أدري
I'm not satisfied either!
!لا يروق لي الأمر
Nami! I can't believe you kicked me down the slope!
!نامي! كيف تجرئين على ركلي هناك؟
Usopp, you jerk!
!أوسوب أيّها الوغد
You didn't say which way was north!
!لم تخبرني أين كان الشمال
Who are these guys?
من هذان؟
They're late...
...تأخروا
I thought they knew full well what happens to those who derail my plans.
.ظننتُهم يدركون مصيرَ من يعيق خططي
Taking their sweet time like this...
...كيف يجرؤون على التباطؤ
Well, if they've forgotten even that…
،إن كانوا نسوا ذلك
then I'll slaughter them all!
!فسأقتلهم جميعًا
Y-You guys are that strong?!
!أ-أنتما بهذه القوة؟
What took you guys so long?!
!تأخرتما بالوصول
You're the one who got me stuck back there!
!أنتِ من أوقعتني هناك
I didn't mean to, okay?! I didn't have a choice!
!كانت تلك حادثة !ما باليد حيلة
Besides, one of us getting free was better than both of us staying stuck.
.نجاةُ أحدنا خيرٌ من هلاكنا
Then you should've stayed!
!كان الأحرى أن تَبقي إذًا
Seriously!
كيف لي أن أعرف أيّ اتجاه هو الشمال من غيره؟
What?!
!ماذا؟
You're the one who ran off all confident!
!أنت من انطلق راكضًا بكل ثقة
Well, I was just trying to help you.
.انطلقت لا شعوريًا
Night is long gone now...
...انقضى الليل تمامًا الآن
and Captain Kuro has a short temper...
.والقبطان كورو لا يتحمل التأخير
Hey, men!
!يا رجال
Don't tell me you couldn't handle two measly brats!
لا يمكن أن يكون هذين !الطّفلين قضيا عليكم، أليس كذلك؟
Listen!
،اسمعوا
We don't have time to be dilly-dallying here!
!لا نملك الوقت للتسكع هنا طوال اليوم
If our enemy is strong, we just need to be even stronger!
،إن كان خصمنا قويًا !فعلينا أن نصبح أقوى
Now watch this ring closely!
!هيّا، راقبوا هذا الحلق جيّدًا
On "one, two, Jango," you guys will grow strong.
،«عندما أقول «واحد، اثنان، جانغو .فستغدون أقوياء
Your wounds will completely heal, and you will grow stronger and stronger!
،ستشفى جراحكم بالكامل !وتصبحون أقوى وأقوى
What are they doing?
ماذا يفعلون؟
It's hypnosis!
!إنّه تنويم مغناطيسي
He's trying to convince them to be stronger!
!إنّه يحاول أن يقنعهم أن يصبحوا أقوى
How ridiculous!
!يا للسخافة
One!
!واحد
Two!
!اثنان
Jango!
!جانغو
No way!
!مستحيل
H-He destroyed part of the cliff!
!حـ-حطّم المنحدر
Talk about power!
!يا لها من قوة
That's some effective hypnosis!
!نُوّموا مغناطيسيًا حقًا
With an army that strong...
...بوجود كلّ هذا العدد منهم بهذه القوّة
Go!
!انطلقوا
Crush anyone who gets in the way!
!اسحقوا ايًّا من يعترض طريقكم
Get back, you guys!
!تراجعا
We'll handle this!
!نحن سنتولى هذا
Hey, Luffy!
...يا لوفي
Luffy?!
!لوفي؟
You got hypnotized too?!
!نُوّمتَ مغناطيسيًا أيضًا؟
He's so simple-minded...!
!يا له من شخص ذو عقل بسيط
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Gatling!
!المدفع الرشاش
Damn you, Captain Kuro...
...تبًا لك أيّها القبطان كورو
Thinking he'd have no impact was a mistake!
!كنت مخطئًا أنّه لن يحدث أيّ تأثير
They're no ordinary brats!
!هؤلاء ليسوا مجرد أطفال عاديين
Where's he off to now?!
!إلى أين سيذهب؟
What's he gonna do?!
ما الذي سيفعله؟
Go, Luffy!
!انطلق يا لوفي
He's gonna destroy the ship!
!سيحطّم السفينة
No, he's not!
!كلّا
He's gonna crush us with it!
.إنّه ينوي سحقنا بهذا
Please do something, Captain!
.أرجوك افعل شيئًا أيّها القبطان
On "one, two, Jango," you'll get sleepy!
!«نم عندما أقول «واحد، اثنان، جانغو
One!
!واحد
Two!
!اثنان
Jango!
!جانغو
Looks like they're just about wiped out!
!يبدو أنه هزمهم
I'd say so.
.نعم
Hey!
!الأهمّ، لوفي عالق هناك
He won't die.
.لن يموت
Just worry about your own wounds.
..اقلق على إصاباتك
Damn that brat!
!فعلها ذلك الطفل
Now the plan is all but ruined!
!أُفسدت الخطة بالكامل الآن
If Captain Kuro saw this,
،إن رأى القبطان كورو هذا
he'd slaughter all of us too!
!فسيقتلنا جميعًا أيضًا
Hey, Buchi!
!يا بوتشي
Come look at this mess!
!انظر لهذا، يا له من أمر جلل
What the hell?!
!ما هذا؟
We still have our trump card!
!ما زال لدينا ورقة رابحة
Come forth, Meowban Brothers!
!تعاليا أيّها الأخوان مياوبان
It is Klahadore from the mansion!
!إنه كلاهادور! خادم القصر
Why is he heading for the shore so early...?!
!لِمَ يسير نحو الساحل في الصباح الباكر؟